Sakura-chan, two more dicks,
さくらちゃん、また2つのチンチン、
Before the hair.
髪の前に
Touch both,
2つとも触って、
Grow it slowly.
ゆ っくり大きくしていってこな
Give me a lick.
ペロペロしてあげな
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってきたね
Put both in your mouth.
2つとも口入れ
Show me your breasts, that's it.
おっぱい見せてごらん、それ
It's amazing, both of them.
すんごいビンビンだね、どっちも
How about Takura-chan?
たくらちゃんどう?
Taro-chan, put it on your breasts.
たろちゃん、おっぱいに出すんだよ
This came out with a lot of sperm.
す んごい精子出たね、これ
Warm.
あったかい
Is it warm?
あったかい?
Yeah.
うん
In addition to Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃんの加えて
This is big.
おっきいね、これ
Kuro-chan, your head is small.
黒ちゃん、頭小さいね、これ
Please lick me deep inside.
奥までいっぱい舐めてもらえ
Kuro-chan is pulling out the inside of her mouth.
黒ちゃんが口の中を抜き出してる
Because it's a limiting image.
限界のイメージだから
Can you try it with just your hands?
手だけでいしてみ?
Kuro-chan doesn't show off people.
人をパンパン出ない黒ちゃん
Did you put out a lot?
いっぱい出した?
It came out really well.
めっちゃ出たね
Did you suck it all up?
全部吸い取れた?
Spirit.
精神
Did you feel good today?
今日気持ちよかった?
Let's all do it again.
またみんなでやろうね
see you.
またね